theapollobox.com 2019-12-02

# Privacy Policy | the Apollo Box - ApolloBox

This privacy policy explains how Apollo Box uses and protects any and all of the information that you give Apollo Box when you use our website. When and if we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

By visiting Apollo Box’s website or using Apollo Box's mobile applications, you are accepting the terms of this Privacy Policy. Apollo Box may change this policy from time to time by updating this page and we reserve the right to change this privacy policy at any time. Check this page from time to time to ensure that you understand any changes. If you have any questions, you can contact us via email contact@theapollobox.com. 

#### 1\. Information We Collect

We collect information from our customers to better process orders and serve them. 

When you sign up, the information we collect can include your name, shipping address, billing address, telephone number/s, e-mail address, and payment information such as your credit card number. To safeguard that your username and password remain confidential, DO NOT share this information with anyone. 

You may also connect to Apollo Box through an external application/website account. Be aware that in that case Apollo Box may receive information from that external source (information could include your photos, likes, comments, friends, communities, etc). After you receive an item from us, Apollo Box also records information like what you buy, what you like, and other preferences. We may also use cookies and log files to store your information. 

#### 2\. What We Do With the Information We Gather

We acquire this information to better understand your needs and provide you with a better service.

We also may use the information to improve our products and services. As a result of collecting your information, we may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize our website according to your interests. To safeguard the confidentiality of your username and password, DO NOT share this information with anyone else. We allow third-party companies to collect non-personally identifiable information when customers visit our site. These companies typically use a cookie or web beacon to collect this information in order to provide advertisements likely to be of interest to you. Our site does not respond to “Do Not Track” signals or mechanisms.

#### 3\. Sharing

We want to respect your privacy. Apollo Box will not disclose your name, email address or other personal information to third parties without your explicit consent, except as specified in this policy. Apollo Box limits access to your personal information to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

We may employ third party companies to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include order fulfillment, package delivery, marketing assistance, postal and e-mail delivery, customer service, data analysis, and credit processing. The third parties we contract for these purposes have limited access to your personal information and may not use it for other purposes.

We may frame or mask another website so that the look, feel and interface simulate the experience of browsing a genuine www.theapollobox.com web page. Extreme care and discretion is exercised when evaluating third party sites. We only brand third party sites if their organization applies stringent security and privacy practices which parallel our own commitment to safe online shopping.

As our business continues to evolve, we may acquire or sell business units or subsidiaries.Customer information is one of the business assets that would be transferred in these types of transactions. In such a situation, your personally identifiable information would only be used in a manner consistent with our pre-existing Privacy Notice. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law, and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. 

#### 4\. Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Apollo Box is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware of privacy policies of other sites when they leave our site, and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects their personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website. Third-party plug-ins also may collect information about your use of the Site. Apollo Box has no control of these third-party plug-ins and they are not covered by our privacy policy.

#### 5\. Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Your Apollo Box account information is protected by a password. It is important that you protect against unauthorized access of your account and information by choosing your password carefully, and keeping your password and computer secure by signing out after using our services.

#### 6\. Data Retention

Apollo Box will retain your information only for as long as is necessary or your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you no longer want Apollo Box to use your information to provide you services, you may close your account. Apollo Box will only retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. You may inform us of any changes or requests in regards to your personal data, and in accordance with our obligations under local data protection law, we may update or delete your personal data accordingly.

#### 7\. Correction/Updating/Reviewing Personal Information

Customers may change or review their stored account information such as street address or e-mail address through our website by logging into their personal accounts. You must have your username and password in order to access your account. In the event you forget both your username and password, please contact our customer service department for assistance.

#### 8\. How We Use Cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and after we use your date that data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not.A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

#### 9\. Log Files

Apollo Box may gather certain information and store in it in log files. Information stored includes IP addresses, Internet service provider, referring pages, operating system, browser type, time stamp, and etc.

#### 10\. Controlling Your Personal Information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information by emailing us at contact@theapollobox.com. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee may apply. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to contact@theapollobox.com. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please contact us as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

Questions: Should you have any aditional questions regarding these Terms you may contact us at contact@theapollobox.com.
